gtplanet.net 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy – GTPlanet

GTPlanet has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This site contains links to other sites. GTPlanet is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

## Information We Hold

The type of data we process and collect includes:

  * Your name or username
  * Your email address
  * Your IP address
  * Your billing/shipping address
  * Basic payment information (we **do not** store credit card numbers)

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as any profile fields you complete on your profile. We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * When you register as a member of this site
  * You fill out our contact form
  * You browse the site (see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.gtplanet.net/forum/help/cookies) for more information)
  * You fill out fields on your profile
  * You purchase a product or service from us

## How Your Information Is Used

We may use your information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.
  * We may use your address to verify payment details or shipping information.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you’re using.

## Email Opt-In/Opt-Out

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails [in your profile](https://www.gtplanet.net/forum/account/contact-details).

All emails sent by GTPlanet also include links with instructions on how to disable or opt-out from further mailings.

## Keeping Your Information Secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

## Common ID Cookie

This site uses cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie to provide its services. Cookies are important devices for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user id in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID that can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie by clicking here.

## Advertising Privacy Settings

When you use our site, pre-selected companies may access and use certain information on your device and about your interests to serve ads or personalized content. You may revisit or change consent-choices at any time by clicking here.

## Right To Access Personal Data

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please [contact us](http://www.gtplanet.net/contact). If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may ask us to complete or correct that information. You also have the option to change or modify information previously provided [in your account settings](https://www.gtplanet.net/forum/account/personal-details).

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please [contact us](http://www.gtplanet.net/contact) if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Public **Forums**

This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. GTPlanet cannot be held responsible in any way for any information posted or otherwise distributed by public users via its chat or forum mediums.

## Third Party Advertising

We use various third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

## Acceptance Of This Policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time.

## Contacting GTPlanet

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us online](https://www.gtplanet.net/contact) (webmastergtplanet.net) or via the address below:

GTPlanet Networks  
P.O. Box 755  
London, KY 40743
